<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Smart Dating</title>
    <link>http://smart-dating.online/personality/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Smart Dating</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2008 - 2014, all rights reserved.</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="http://smart-dating.online/personality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>You are an Achiever</title>
      <link>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/achiever/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/achiever/</guid>
      <description>Achievers are energetic thrillseekers who are at their best when putting out fires, whether literal or metaphorical. They bring a sense of dynamic energy to their interactions with others and the world around them. They assess situations quickly and move adeptly to respond to immediate problems with practical solutions.
Active and playful, Achievers are often the life of the party and have a good sense of humor. They use their keen powers of observation to assess their audience and adapt quickly to keep interactions exciting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artist</title>
      <link>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/artist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/artist/</guid>
      <description>Artists are gentle caretakers who live in the present moment and enjoy their surroundings with cheerful, low-key enthusiasm. They are flexible and spontaneous, and like to go with the flow to enjoy what life has to offer. Artists are quiet and unassuming, and may be hard to get to know. However, to those who know them well, the Artist is warm and friendly, eager to share in life&amp;rsquo;s many experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Captain</title>
      <link>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/captain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/captain/</guid>
      <description>Captains are strategic leaders, motivated to organize change. They are quick to see inefficiency and conceptualize new solutions, and enjoy developing long-range plans to accomplish their vision. They excel at logical reasoning and are usually articulate and quick-witted.
Captains are analytical and objective, and like bringing order to the world around them. When there are flaws in a system, the Captain sees them, and enjoys the process of discovering and implementing a better way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheerleader</title>
      <link>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/cheerleader/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/cheerleader/</guid>
      <description>Cheerleaders are people-centered creators with a focus on possibilities and a contagious enthusiasm for new ideas, people and activities. Energetic, warm, and passionate, Cheerleaders love to help other people explore their creative potential.
Cheerleaders are typically agile and expressive communicators, using their wit, humor, and mastery of language to create engaging stories. Imaginative and original, Cheerleaders often have a strong artistic side. They are drawn to art because of its ability to express inventive ideas and create a deeper understanding of human experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Craftman</title>
      <link>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/craftman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/craftman/</guid>
      <description>Craftmans are observant artisans with an understanding of mechanics and an interest in troubleshooting. They approach their environments with a flexible logic, looking for practical solutions to the problems at hand. They are independent and adaptable, and typically interact with the world around them in a self-directed, spontaneous manner.
Craftmans are attentive to details and responsive to the demands of the world around them. Because of their astute sense of their environment, they are good at moving quickly and responding to emergencies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diplomat</title>
      <link>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/diplomat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/diplomat/</guid>
      <description>Diplomats are conscientious helpers, sensitive to the needs of others and energetically dedicated to their responsibilities. They are highly attuned to their emotional environment and attentive to both the feelings of others and the perception others have of them. Diplomats like a sense of harmony and cooperation around them, and are eager to please and provide.
Diplomats value loyalty and tradition, and usually make their family and friends their top priority.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Director</title>
      <link>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/director/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/director/</guid>
      <description>Directors are hardworking traditionalists, eager to take charge in organizing projects and people. Orderly, rule-abiding, and conscientious, Directors like to get things done, and tend to go about projects in a systematic, methodical way.
Directors are the consummate organizers, and want to bring structure to their surroundings. They value predictability and prefer things to proceed in a logical order. When they see a lack of organization, the Director often takes the initiative to establish processes and guidelines, so that everyone knows what&amp;rsquo;s expected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainer</title>
      <link>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/entertainer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/entertainer/</guid>
      <description>Entertainers are vivacious entertainers who charm and engage those around them. They are spontaneous, energetic, and fun-loving, and take pleasure in the things around them: food, clothes, nature, animals, and especially people.
Entertainers are typically warm and talkative and have a contagious enthusiasm for life. They like to be in the middle of the action and the center of attention. They have a playful, open sense of humor, and like to draw out other people and help them have a good time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guardian</title>
      <link>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/guardian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/guardian/</guid>
      <description>Guardians are industrious caretakers, loyal to traditions and organizations. They are practical, compassionate, and caring, and are motivated to provide for others and protect them from the perils of life.
Guardians are conventional and grounded, and enjoy contributing to established structures of society. They are steady and committed workers with a deep sense of responsibility to others. They focus on fulfilling their duties, particularly when they are taking care of the needs of other people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hero</title>
      <link>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/hero/</guid>
      <description>Heroes are idealist organizers, driven to implement their vision of what is best for humanity. They often act as catalysts for human growth because of their ability to see potential in other people and their charisma in persuading others to their ideas. They are focused on values and vision, and are passionate about the possibilities for people.
Heroes are typically energetic and driven, and often have a lot on their plates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Innovator</title>
      <link>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/innovator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/innovator/</guid>
      <description>Innovators are inspired innovators, motivated to find new solutions to intellectually challenging problems. They are curious and clever, and seek to comprehend the people, systems, and principles that surround them. Open-minded and unconventional, Visionaries want to analyze, understand, and influence other people.
Innovators enjoy playing with ideas and especially like to banter with others. They use their quick wit and command of language to keep the upper hand with other people, often cheerfully poking fun at their habits and eccentricities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mentor</title>
      <link>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/mentor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/mentor/</guid>
      <description>Mentors are creative nurturers with a strong sense of personal integrity and a drive to help others realize their potential. Creative and dedicated, they have a talent for helping others with original solutions to their personal challenges.
The Counselor has a unique ability to intuit others&amp;rsquo; emotions and motivations, and will often know how someone else is feeling before that person knows it himself. They trust their insights about others and have strong faith in their ability to read people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimist</title>
      <link>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/optimist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/optimist/</guid>
      <description>Optimists are imaginative idealists, guided by their own core values and beliefs. To a Healer, possibilities are paramount; the realism of the moment is only of passing concern. They see potential for a better future, and pursue truth and meaning with their own individual flair.
Optimists are sensitive, caring, and compassionate, and are deeply concerned with the personal growth of themselves and others. Individualistic and nonjudgmental, Optimists believe that each person must find their own path.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philosopher</title>
      <link>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/philosopher/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/philosopher/</guid>
      <description>Philosophers are philosophical innovators, fascinated by logical analysis, systems, and design. They are preoccupied with theory, and search for the universal law behind everything they see. They want to understand the unifying themes of life, in all their complexity.
Philosophers are detached, analytical observers who can seem oblivious to the world around them because they are so deeply absorbed in thought. They spend much of their time focused internally: exploring concepts, making connections, and seeking understanding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strategist</title>
      <link>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/strategist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/strategist/</guid>
      <description>Strategists are analytical problem-solvers, eager to improve systems and processes with their innovative ideas. They have a talent for seeing possibilities for improvement, whether at work, at home, or in themselves.
Often intellectual, Strategists enjoy logical reasoning and complex problem-solving. They approach life by analyzing the theory behind what they see, and are typically focused inward, on their own thoughtful study of the world around them. Strategists are drawn to logical systems and are much less comfortable with the unpredictable nature of other people and their emotions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tactician</title>
      <link>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/tactician/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://smart-dating.online/personality/types/tactician/</guid>
      <description>Tacticians are responsible organizers, driven to create and enforce order within systems and institutions. They are neat and orderly, inside and out, and tend to have a procedure for everything they do. Reliable and dutiful, Tacticians want to uphold tradition and follow regulations.
Tacticians are steady, productive contributors. Although they are Introverted, Tacticians are rarely isolated; typical Tacticians know just where they belong in life, and want to understand how they can participate in established organizations and systems.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>